{
  "questions" : [{
    "question" : "1",
    "answer": "1",
    "score_increment" : 10,
    "score_decrement" : 5,
    "zone" : 1
    },
    {
    "question" : "2",
    "answer": "2",
    "score_increment" : 20,
    "score_decrement" : 10,
    "zone" : 1
    }, {
    "question" : "3",
    "answer": "3",
    "score_increment" : 30,
    "score_decrement" : 15,
    "zone" : 1
    }, {
    "question" : "1",
    "answer": "1",
    "score_increment" : 10,
    "score_decrement" : 5,
    "zone" : 2
    },
    {
    "question" : "2",
    "answer": "2",
    "score_increment" : 20,
    "score_decrement" : 10,
    "zone" : 2
    }, {
    "question" : "3",
    "answer": "3",
    "score_increment" : 30,
    "score_decrement" : 15,
    "zone" : 2
    },{
    "question" : "1",
    "answer": "1",
    "score_increment" : 10,
    "score_decrement" : 5,
    "zone" : 3
    },
    {
    "question" : "2",
    "answer": "2",
    "score_increment" : 20,
    "score_decrement" : 10,
    "zone" : 3
    }, {
    "question" : "3",
    "answer": "3",
    "score_increment" : 30,
    "score_decrement" : 15,
    "zone" : 3
    },{
    "question" : "1",
    "answer": "1",
    "score_increment" : 10,
    "score_decrement" : 5,
    "zone" : 4
    },
    {
    "question" : "2",
    "answer": "2",
    "score_increment" : 20,
    "score_decrement" : 10,
    "zone" : 4
    }, {
    "question" : "3",
    "answer": "3",
    "score_increment" : 30,
    "score_decrement" : 15,
    "zone" : 4
    },{
    "question" : "1",
    "answer": "1",
    "score_increment" : 10,
    "score_decrement" : 5,
    "zone" : 5
    },
    {
    "question" : "2",
    "answer": "2",
    "score_increment" : 20,
    "score_decrement" : 10,
    "zone" : 5
    }, {
    "question" : "3",
    "answer": "3",
    "score_increment" : 30,
    "score_decrement" : 15,
    "zone" : 5
    },{
    "question" : "1",
    "answer": "1",
    "score_increment" : 10,
    "score_decrement" : 5,
    "zone" : 6
    },
    {
    "question" : "2",
    "answer": "2",
    "score_increment" : 20,
    "score_decrement" : 10,
    "zone" : 6
    }, {
    "question" : "3",
    "answer": "3",
    "score_increment" : 30,
    "score_decrement" : 15,
    "zone" : 6
    }]
}